http://www.naepc.org/about/privacy

Hartman Axley Lifetime Service Award
Volunteer!
Hartman Axley Lifetime Service Award
Volunteer!
Privacy Policy
At the National Association of Estate Planners & Councils (NAEPC) and The NAEPC Education Foundation (the Foundation), protecting your privacy and the confidentiality of your personal information is one of our primary concerns.  When you use our web site, we strive to make sure that any personal information you provide to us is protected.  We believe it is important that you know how we treat the information about you that we receive on the Internet.  Please read our statement below for more detailed information.
Acceptable Uses of Your Information
NAEPC and the Foundation may use council membership information to periodically broadcast newsletters, including national conference announcements.  This is done only with the written permission of your local council.  Each recipient of such a message will have the option to permanently unsubscribe from future communications from NAEPC and the Foundation without changing their relationship with their local council.
Our Commitment to You
The relationship between NAEPC, the Foundation, and NAEPC’s Councils and members is extremely important to us.  We strive to maintain your trust and confidence in our association, an essential aspect of which is our commitment to protect your personal information to the best of our ability.  We believe that you value your privacy, so we will not intentionally disclose your personal information to anyone unless it is required by law, is at your direction, or is permitted by law and necessary to provide you with our services.  We have not and will not sell your personal information to anyone.
The Personal Information That We Collect and Communicate
The primary reason that we collect and maintain your personal information is to serve you and administer our relationship with you.  The types and categories of information we collect about you include:
Information we receive from you on applications and other forms to join our membership or that is provided by your Council to populate its web site such as your name, address, telephone number, discipline, and other relevant information; and
Information about your transactions with us such as conference registrations.
We may disclose the personal information that we collect to companies that perform administrative functions for us such as sending The AEP ALERT, the NAEPC Journal of Tax & Estate Planning, and annual statements for At-Large dues and AEP and EPLS Annual Dues & Recertification forms.
How to Contact Us
Our relationship with you is our most important asset.  You entrust us with your personal information, and we do everything we can to maintain that trust.  If you have any questions or concerns about our use of your personal information, please e-mail us at admin@naepc.org, or call us at (866) 226-2224, or contact your Council Administrator directly.
NAEPC and the Foundation will mail a copy of this privacy notice to all existing councils and designation holders no later than May 30, 2007.  All new councils and designation holders will receive a copy of this privacy notice starting on May 30, 2007.
About
AEP®
EPLS
Councils
Publications
Events
Benefits
Public
